Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Evelyn Seinfeld, "Chronology of the New York City Fiscal Crisis, July 18, 1974 to April 4, 1977." DC 37: Department of Research and Negotiations, 1977.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact nyuspecialcollections@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
AFSCME, DC 37 Photographs (Photos 247)
AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1306 Records (WAG 290)
AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930 Records (WAG 40)
AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930: Ray Markey Files (WAG 286)
AFSCME, DC 37, Local 420 Records (WAG 215)
Bernard and Jewel Bellush Papers (WAG 30)
Civil Service Technical Guild Records (WAG 24)
Social Service Employees Union Records (WAG 3)
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains constitutions, minutes, correspondence, reports, newsletters, leaflets, websitesand printed material documenting the history of DC 37 from 1957 to 2000s, with significant coverage of the 1950s to early 1980s. The materials chronicle the tenure of executive directors Jerry Wurf, Calogero Taibi, Victor Gotbaum, and Stanley Hill, as well as the leadership of associate director Lillian Roberts (who returned to DC 37 in 2002 as executive director). Also represented are records of DC 37's Legal Department, including files on its advocacy for women's pay equity, and records of the Communications Department, documenting the union's newspaper, Public Employee Press. In addition, the collection contains eight boxes of audio reels and cassettes, the bulk of which are recordings of DC 37's radio show "It's Your City, It's Our Job."
Series I: Constitution and Minutes, 1955-2004, includes a copy of DC 37's constitution as well as minutes of the Executive Board and Delegates from 1955 to 2004. Minutes on paper are available for the years 1955-1960, 1970-1979 and 2001-2004, while 1961-1969 are available only on microfilm (R-7424). Holdings for the 1980s and 1990s are incomplete. A limited number of minutes of the Finance Committee and Trustees are also represented in the series.
Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999.
Subseries II:A: Stanley Hill Executive Director Records, 1987-1999, contains correspondence, reports, and printed material from Hill's tenure as executive director from 1986 to 1998. Although most material in this subseries is from his last two years in office, some earlier items are also present, including extensive coverage of New York City's 1991 fiscal crisis that led to layoffs and wage deferrals for DC 37 members. Two other layoff crises--the 1996 threat by Mayor Rudolph Giuliani to close some of New York City's municipal hospitals and the 1998 budget cuts affecting Health and Hospitals Corporation employees--are also well documented in this subseries. In addition to Hill's correspondence with numerous DC 37 locals, this subseries also demonstrates growing attention paid to the HIV/AIDS crisis by city agencies and nonprofits and Hill's involvement with a number of outside organizations, including the American Committee on Africa, Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, and One Hundred Black Men. Although Hill left DC 37 in December 1998, the files contain a few records from late 1998 and early 1999, which reflect ongoing projects carried out by Hill's executive assistant, Brenda White.
Subseries II:B: Lillian Roberts Associate Director Records, 1951-1983, provides nearly complete documentation of Lillian Roberts' influential tenure as Associate Director from 1965 to 1982, including correspondence, reports, speeches, and printed material. While the subseries chronicles Roberts' oversight of division directors and personnel at DC 37 headquarters, it most thoroughly documents her close connection to Local 420 and her role in its ongoing negotiations with the Health and Hospitals Corporation. Highlights include material on the 1965 representation election of hospital aides; the successful implementation of a training program to upgrade nurse's aides to LPNs; layoffs of hospital workers during the 1975 fiscal crisis; the hospital workers' strike of 1976; the affiliation of municipal and voluntary hospitals; and Roberts' disputes with Local 420 president James Butler in 1978 and 1979. Also of interest is material on the use of welfare recipients as workers in city agencies through the Work Incentive Program and the Work Relief Employment Program; establishment of DC 37's Education Fund; application of the Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) in New York City; and several trips by DC 37 members to Africa that Roberts led in the mid-1970s.
Series III: Legal Department Records, 1956-1986, contains legal documents, correspondence, notes, reports, printed material, and newspaper clippings. It provides a snapshot of the Legal Department's multi-faceted work under the leadership of lead counsels Julius Topol and Beverly Gross in the 1970s and early 1980s, from arbitration of grievances to litigation on major social issues of the period. Significant cases represented are James Butler v. DC 37, resulting from Gotbaum and Roberts' dispute with Local 420 President Butler; Daniel Mando, et al. v. Abraham Beame, et al., concerning representation rights for employees hired under the Emergency Employment Act of 1971; and Women in City Government United, et al. v. City of New York, et al., a successful gender discrimination suit challenging the city's use of sex-specific actuarial tables to determine pension contributions and payments. The files also contain material on CSTG's attempt under president Richard Izzo to disaffiliate from DC 37 and on the Deferral Payment Agreement of 1982, under which the city addressed its overdue promise to repay city workers wages deferred during the 1975 fiscal crisis. A significant group of files on pay equity issues from the late 1970s and early 1980s were compiled by Audrey Browne, a Legal Department attorney. They include numerous reports on pay equity issues in New York City and around the country, as well as legal documents relating to AFSCME, et al. v. State of Washington.
Series IV: Communications Department Records, 1963-2004.
Subseries IV:A: Edward Handman Records, 1972-1991, include reports, transcripts, and newspaper clippings compiled by Handman, who served as Director of Public Relations and Publications from 1972 until the early 1990s. Of particular note in this subseries is extensive coverage of two fiscal crises in New York City: the prolonged crisis of the mid-1970s and the shorter but still acute budget crisis of 1991. Handman helped DC 37 craft its response to public perceptions that inflated wages, benefits, and pensions of city workers were responsible for the city's strained budgets.
Subseries IV:B: Bill Schleicher Records, 1992-2004, contains reports, notes, and newspaper clippings compiled by Schleicher in the course of his duties as editor of Public Employee Press(PEP). These materials include annotated minutes of and notes on meetings of delegates, division and department leaders, shop stewards, and the executive board from 2001 to 2004. Of particular note are collected materials--primarily printed materials and reports--on multiple investigations beginning in 1998 by the Manhattan District Attorney of corruption inside DC 37 and its locals. The subseries also contains Schleicher's research material on a variety of local and national issues such as the city budget, contract negotiations, and immigration.
Subseries IV:C: Public Employee Press Research Files, 1963-1993, contains paper records separated from the Public Employee Press photograph files in the DC 37 Photograph Collection (NP #247). These include notes, reports, and copies of documents relating to issues affecting the union as reported by PEP staff, primarily during the 1960s and 1970s. Key issues addressed include safety issues, the union's exposé of poor conditions at the city's public hospitals, the citywide strike of the union's blue collar locals in 1971, the affiliation of municipal and voluntary hospitals, and the contentious representation election of school aides waged by the UFT against DC 37 in 1973.
Series V: General Files, 1944-2000, consists primarily of records kept by DC 37's executive office and printing department from the mid-1950s to the 1970s. This series contains the oldest records in the collection and provides the only documentation of the administrations of executive directors Jerry Wurf, Calogero Taibi, and Victor Gotbaum. Files for nearly every local in the union are present, containing correspondence with executive office staff, salary appeal briefs (predating collective bargaining agreements), minutes, newsletters, printed material such as meeting notices and leaflets, and occasionally constitutions and contracts. Some locals are better represented than others. This series documents key moments in DC 37 history, including the early activism of Locals 149 (Parks) and 299 (Recreation), the 1961 strike of employees at the Bronx Zoo and Coney Island Aquarium, the 1965 welfare workers' strike of Local 371 and SSEU, the 1965 hospital aides representation election, and the 1976 hospital workers' strike. DC 37's Political Action and Legislation Department is also well represented in this series, chronicling the union's growing political strength in the 1970s and 1980s.
Series VI: Restricted Materials, 1967-1997. (Closed for 50 years from date of creation.)
Series VII: Ken Nash Collection - Audio Reels, 1977-1990, contains audio tape reels collected by DC 37's Ken Nash, who was a producer and host of the radio show, "Building Bridges: Your Community & Labor Report." This series is organized into three subseries; the bulk are reels of DC 37's radio show "It's Your City, It's Our Job."
Series VIII: Ken Nash Collection - Audio Cassettes, 1986-1999, contains audio cassettes collected by DC 37's Ken Nash, who was a producer and host of the radio show, "Building Bridges: Your Community & Labor Report." This series is organized into six subseries; the bulk are cassettes of DC 37's radio show "It's Your City, It's Our Job."
Series IX: Ken Nash Collection - 2015 Donation, 1993-2014, contains audio recordings of DC 37's radio programs donated by Ken Nash. These recordings cover conferences, interviews with labor leaders, topics related social justice and workers rights, and other events related to District 37 union activity between 1993 and 2003. This series also contains a small amount of ephemera from union related anniversary celebrations and award banquets from 2012-2014.
Series X: Audio Reels - Other, 1965, includes 40 audio reels that appear to be radio spots. Some are in Spanish. These audio reels came to Tamiment with the DC 37 Photographs collection.
Series XI: Archived Websites, includes the main DC 37 website, back issues of their publication Public Employee Press, their blog, and their COVID-19 response website.
Separated Materials
Photographs, graphic materials (cartoons, drawings, etc.), and films from the Communicatoins Department were separated into three collections:
American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Photographs (PHOTOS 247)
American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Graphics (GRAPHICS 34)
American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Films (FILMS 10)
Municipal officials and employees |x Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Correspondence.; Minutes (administrative records); Newsletters.; Civil service -- New York (N.Y.); Audiocassettes.; New York (N.Y.).; Finance, Public |z New York (State) |z New York.; Government employee unions -- New York (State) -- New York; New York (N.Y.) -- Politics and government -- 1951-; Audiotapes.; New York (N.Y.) |x Officials and employees.; Collective bargaining |x Government employees |z New York (State) |z New York; New York (N.Y.) |x Economic conditions.; African Americans and labor unions.; Nurses' aides.; Fliers (printed matter); Pay equity.; White collar workers |x Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions; Labor unions |x Corrupt practices.; Labor unions |x Public relations |z United States.; Labor unions -- Political activity -- United States.; Clippings (information artifacts); Handman, Edward, 1924-; Hill, Stanley, 1936-; Gotbaum, Victor; Taibi, Calogero; Wurf, Jerry, 1919-; Roberts, Lillian; Schleicher, Bill; AFSCME; New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation; New York (N.Y.). Board of Education; AFSCME. District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); Roberts, Lillian; Nash, Ken
- Series I: Constitution and Minutes, 1955-2004
  - Constitution, undated, 1971; cuid4205 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Delegates, undated, 1955-1956; cuid4206 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1957; cuid4207 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1958; cuid4208 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1959-1960; cuid4209 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1960-1968; cuid4210 (Film R-7424)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1970-1973; cuid4211 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1974-1975; cuid4212 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1976; cuid4213 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1977-1978; cuid4214 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1979; cuid4215 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1982; cuid4216 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1991; cuid4217 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 1998-1999; cuid4218 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 2001-2002; cuid4219 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 2003; cuid4220 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: Delegates, 2004; cuid4221 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1956-1957; cuid4222 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1958; cuid4223 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1959; cuid4224 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1959-1968; cuid4225 (Film R-7424)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1960; cuid4226 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1961-1962; cuid4227 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1970-1972; cuid4228 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1973-1974; cuid4229 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1975-1976; cuid4230 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1977-1978; cuid4231 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1979; cuid4232 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1982; cuid4233 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1990-Jun 1991; cuid4234 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, Jul 1991-Dec 1991; cuid4235 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 1996, 1998; cuid4236 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 2001-2003; cuid4237 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Minutes: Executive Board, 2004; cuid4238 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1971; cuid4239 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1972; cuid4240 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1973; cuid4241 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1974; cuid4242 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1975; cuid4243 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1976; cuid4244 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, 1977; cuid4245 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jan 1978-Jun 1978; cuid4246 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jul 1978-Dec 1978; cuid4247 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jan 1979-Jun 1979; cuid4248 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jul 1979-Dec 1979; cuid4249 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jan 1991-Jun 1991; cuid4250 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Minutes: Finance Committee, Jul 1991-Dec 1991; cuid4251 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Minutes: Trustees, 1965; cuid4252 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999
  - Subseries II:A: Stanley Hill Executive Director Records, 1987-1999.
    - Address Book, undated; cuid4253 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Agenda for Children Tomorrow, 1995-1996; cuid4254 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - American Committee on Africa (ACOA): Correspondence, 1991, 1996-Jun 1997; cuid4255 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - ACOA: Correspondence, Jul 1997-1998; cuid4256 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - ACOA: Press Releases and Printed Material, 1996-1998; cuid4257 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1997-1998; cuid4258 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) (Albany, NY), 1991, 1997-1998; cuid4259 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - AFSCME (Washington, D.C.), 1990-1991, 1995-1996; cuid4260 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - AFSCME (Washington, D.C.) I, 1996-1998; cuid4261 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - AFSCME (Washington, D.C.) II, 1996-1998; cuid4262 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - AFSCME: Employee's Pension Plan, 1998; cuid4263 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - AFSCME: Lobby Day, 1998; cuid4264 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - AFSCME: Press Releases and Printed Material, 1991, 1997-1998; cuid4265 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - AFSCME International Conventions, 1996, 1998; cuid4266 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - AFSCME PEOPLE Program, 1996-1998; cuid4267 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - AFSCME Task Force for the Future I, 1996-1998; cuid4268 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - AFSCME Task Force for the Future II, 1996-1998; cuid4269 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - AFSCME, Council 13, 1997; cuid4270 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - AFSCME, Council 20, 1998; cuid4271 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - AFSCME, Council 82 (Security and Law Enforcement Employees), 1990; cuid4272 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - AFSCME, District Council 1707, 1990; cuid4273 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance, 1996-1998; cuid4274 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Association for a Better New York, 1998; cuid4275 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Association for Union Democracy, 1998; cuid4276 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Bellevue Hospital Center, 1997-1998; cuid4277 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bellevue Hospital Community Board, 1991, 1996; cuid4278 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Benefits Trust Fund, 1990-1991, 1996-1997; cuid4279 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Black History Month, 1991, 1997-1998; cuid4280 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Black History Month, 1998-1999; cuid4281 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Black Leadership Commission on AIDS, 1996-1998; cuid4282 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Blue Collar Division, 1996-1998; cuid4283 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Blue Collar Division: Contract Issues, 1994, 1996; cuid4284 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Blue Collar Division: Reports, 1996; cuid4285 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Blue Collar Division: Schedules, 1996-1997; cuid4286 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Bridge and Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association v. Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (Lukas et al. v. Ascher et al.), 1996; cuid4287 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Campaign to Save our Public Hospitals, 1996-1997; cuid4288 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Campaign to Save our Public Hospitals (Oversize), 1996-1997; cuid4289 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Center on AIDS, Drugs and Community Health, 1997; cuid4290 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Central Park Conservancy, 1997-1998; cuid4291 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Child Care Services, 1997; cuid4292 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Citizenship Program, 1996-1998; cuid4293 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - City Project (Alter Budget), 1998; cuid4294 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - City University of New York (CUNY), 1991, 1995; cuid4295 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - CUNY: Collective Bargaining, 1996-1998; cuid4296 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Citywide Administrative Services, 1996-1998; cuid4297 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Citywide Employee Orientation Manual, 1998; cuid4298 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Clerical Division, 1991, 1996-1997; cuid4299 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Clerical Division: Job Center Reports, 1997-1998; cuid4300 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Clippings, 1991; cuid4301 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU), New York Chapter, 1991, 1997-1998; cuid4302 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - CBTU Convention (Minneapolis), 1997-1998; cuid4303 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Coalition on Economic Priorities, 1990-1991; cuid4304 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Collective Bargaining: General, 1990, 1995-1997; cuid4305 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Commission on the Public's Health System, 1997-1998; cuid4306 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Committee for Real Change in DC 37 (Reform Coalition), 1998; cuid4307 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Coney Island Hospital, 1991, 1996-1997; cuid4308 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Contract Negotiations and Settlement: Citywide DC 37 and IBT Local 237, 1990-1991; cuid4309 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Cornell University: Trade Union Women's Studies Program, 1991; cuid4310 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: General, 1990-Mar 1991; cuid4311 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: General, Apr 1991-Sep 1991; cuid4312 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: General, 1996-1997; cuid4313 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: General, 1998; cuid4314 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Internal, 1990-1991, 1995-1999; cuid4315 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Council for Unity, 1996-1998; cuid4316 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1990-1991, 1995-1998; cuid4317 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Domestic Partners/COBRA Settlement, 1993; cuid4318 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Education Department, 1990-1991; cuid4319 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Education Fund, 1990-1991, 1996-1998; cuid4320 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Empire BlueCross BlueShield, 1996-1998; cuid4321 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Empire BlueCross BlueShield: Annual Reports, 1997-1998; cuid4322 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Employee Recognition/Staff Holiday Party, 1996-1998; cuid4323 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Ethical Practices Code, undated; cuid4324 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Excelsior Capital Corporation: Policy Advisory Committee, 1990; cuid4325 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Executive Board: Correspondence, 1990-1992; cuid4326 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Financial Reports, 1997; cuid4327 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Financial Statements and Budgets, 1997-1998; cuid4328 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Fire Department of New York, 1998; cuid4329 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Greater New York Hospital Association, 1997-1998; cuid4330 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Harlem Hospital, 1997-1998; cuid4331 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Health and Security Department, 1991, 1996-1997; cuid4332 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Health and Security Plan, 1990-1991 1998; cuid4333 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Health Care Reform, 1991, 1994-1998; cuid4334 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Health Systems Agency of New York City I, 1990, 1996; cuid4335 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Health Systems Agency of New York City II, 1990, 1996; cuid4336 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - HIP Foundation, 1997-1998; cuid4337 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - HIP Health Plans, 1991, 1996-1997; cuid4338 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - HIP Health Plans, 1998; cuid4339 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - HIV/AIDS, 1990, 1996-1997; cuid4340 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Hill, Stanley: Newspaper Coverage, 1996, 1998; cuid4341 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Hill, Stanley et al v. Rudolph Giuliani (Hospital Closures), 1996; cuid4342 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hospital Association of New York State: Regulatory Reform, 1991; cuid4343 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Hospital Support Sunday, 1996; cuid4344 (Box 5, Folder 9)